cricwindow.com 2015-06-16

# Privacy Policy of cricwindow.com

|  |   
---  
|   
---  
|   
---  
Advertisement  
|   
---  
| Advertisement  
---  
|   
---  
  |  |   
---  
|  |   
---  
Privacy Policy  
|   
---  
| www.cricwindow.com  
---  
Privacy Policy  
  
Please note that this Policy is only applicable to the users of the Website and the information and data gathered on the Website and not to any other information or website. You are hereby advised to read this Policy carefully and fully understand the nature and purpose of gathering and/or collecting sensitive, personal and other information and the usage, disclosure and sharing of such information. At www.cricwindow.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.cricwindow.com and how it is used.  

Third Party Websites  
  
If you click on a link to a third party site or otherwise leave the Website, you will go to a website that is outside the purview of our control. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your Personal Information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security practices as we do. The use of Personal Information by such websites shall be governed by the privacy policies provided therein. Therefore, if you visit a third party website that is linked to our Website, you should consult that website's privacy policy before providing any Personal Information.  
  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include...Google Adsense.These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.cricwindow.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see. www.cricwindow.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.cricwindow.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  
  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.   

Log Files, Cookies and Web Beacons  
  
Like many other Web sites, www.cricwindow.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  
  
www.cricwindow.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  

DoubleClick DART Cookie  
  
* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.cricwindow.com.  
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.cricwindow.com and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  

Changes to the Policy  
  
The internet is a fast evolving medium and changes to the policy may be necessary to address any future requirements. If we make any changes to the policy, users will be notified of the changes here.  

Applicable Law  
  
This Privacy Policy and information contained herein, shall be governed by the laws of the Republic of India, shall retain exclusive jurisdiction to entertain any proceedings in relation to any disputes arising out of the same.  

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at cricwindow007(at)gmail(dot)com.  

www.cricwindow.com - "Vision to Discover Best Cricket Info"
